

Tanzida Faruk

Business Support Associate

Phone: 01781351830

Address: 192/2 Shantibag, Dhaka

Website: https://bd.linkedin.com/in/tanzida-faruk-b860ba177

Email: tanzidafaruk@gmail.com

The goal is to see myself as successful Chartered Accountant someday. In the meantime, I've consistently engaged in planning and operational improvements for business's growth. Experience in policy development and staff management procedures positively impacting overall morale and productivity. Acting as business interface so as to filter general information, requests and queries. Has considerable experience of providing effective administrative support to various departments including HR, Business Development, Billing and Accounting.

EXPERIENCE

Suzuki Bangladesh| Rancon MotorBikes Ltd.

June, 2019-Present

Business Support Associate

- -Worked and reported directly to the Divisional Managing Directo.
- -Maintains administrative workflow by studying methods; implementing cost reductions; developing reporting procedures.
- -Creates and revises systems and procedures by analyzing operating practices; studying utilization of micro-computer and software technologies; evaluating personnel and technological requirements; implementing changes.
- -Develops administrative staff by providing information, educational opportunities, and coaching.
- -Resolves administrative problems by analyzing information; identifying and communication solutions.
- -Maintains rapport with customers, managers, and employees by arranging continuing contacts; researching and developing new services and methods; setting priorities; resolving problem situations.
- -Maintains suggestion system by directing and controlling administrative technical aspects in accordance with management directives.
- -Provides information by answering questions and requests.
- -Maintains continuity of work operations by documenting and communicating needed actions to management; discovering irregularities; determining continuing needs.
- -Guides employee actions by researching, developing, writing, and updating administrative policies, procedures, methods, and guidelines; communicating developments to management.
- -Completes administrative projects by identifying and implementing new technology and resources; redesigning systems; recommending re-deployment of designated resources.
- Accomplishes department and organization mission by completing related results as needed.

Imprint Dhaka Limited

October, 2017-March, 2019

Customer Service Executive

- -Open and maintain customer accounts by recording account information.
- -Resolve product or service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint; determining the cause of the problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment; following up to ensure resolution.

- -Recommend potential products or services to management by collecting customer information and analyzing custo-Manage large amounts of incoming calls
- -Generate sales leads
- -Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction
- -Build sustainable relationships of trust through open and interactive communication Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods/tools.

EDUCATION

Chartered University College

February 2016- Present

ACCA

British Council 2013-2015

A Levels

Willes Little Flower School

2012-2012

O Levels

SKILLS

- A good communicator
- excellent customer service skills
- exceptional organizational skills
- confident in the team
- problem solver
- always willing to go out of the comfort zone to work more for the betterment of the company
- respectful to others
- full of integrity
- positive attitude
- ability to generate creative content
- ability to think logically
- ability to work under pressure
- always determined to work for society and environment
- quick learner
- always interested to create fashion contents